<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BraGuia</string>
    <string name="add_user" />
    <string name="hint_word">Word...</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save</string>
    <string name="empty_not_saved">Login not saved because it is empty.</string>
    <string name="user"> Username </string>
    <string name="email"> Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password </string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="registar">Não tem conta registada? Registe-se já! </string>
    <string name="fazerLog">Já tem conta registada? Faça login</string>
    <string name="homescreen">Meter cenas aqui </string>
    <string name="registarB">Registar</string>
    <string name="last_name"> Segundo Nome</string>
    <string name="first_name">Primeiro Nome </string>
    <string name="voltar"> Voltar </string>
    <string name="trails"> Roteiros </string>
    <string name="pins"> Pontos Interesse </string>
    <string name="descricao">Welcome to the BraGuia! Whether you\'re a local looking for new places to explore or a visitor discovering the city for the first time, this app has everything you need to make the most of your experience in Braga.With our easy-to-use interface, you can quickly find information on the top attractions, restaurants, and activities in the city. From historic sites like the Braga Cathedral and the Roman ruins of Cividade de Briteiros to modern landmarks such as the famous Bom Jesus do Monte staircase and the contemporary art museum, we\'ve got you covered.Our app also features curated walking tours that take you through the most interesting neighborhoods and hidden gems of the city. You can explore Braga\'s bustling city center, stroll along the peaceful banks of the river, or discover the quaint streets of the medieval town. Each tour is accompanied by detailed maps, insider tips, and historical background information, making it easy to navigate and understand the city\'s rich culture and history.For foodies, we've compiled a list of the best local restaurants, cafes, and bars, where you can taste authentic Portuguese cuisine, sip on a glass of Vinho Verde, or relax with a cup of coffee and a pastry. Whether you're in the mood for traditional dishes like francesinha or cozido, or want to try something new and experimental, our app will guide you to the best dining spots in the city.To make your trip even more enjoyable, we've included practical information on transportation, accommodation, and shopping. You can find the nearest metro or bus station, check hotel reviews and ratings, and discover the best souvenirs and gifts to bring back home. With BraGuia, you can explore Braga like a local and create unforgettable memories.</string>
    <string name="button_start">Let\'s Start!</string>
</resources>